Stan Davis

Games Programmer

Email: stanley.samson.davis@gmail.com

Portfolio: standavis.dev

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic and creatively driven programmer with over 3 years experience in games development. This has provided me an extensive knowledge of various languages, and game engines including C++, C#, and Unity. I have a keen interest in building various gameplay systems, and I am constantly learning new skills through personal development.

Feel free to check out my portfolio to see all of my recent projects.

SKILLS

Languages	Game Engines / APIs	Other Skills
C++	Unity	Git
C#	Godot	Collaboration (Slack/JIRA/Teams/Zoom)
Swift / SwiftUI	Unreal	Web (HTML / CSS)
LUA	DirectX	Video Editing (Premiere Pro)
Rust		Music Production / Sound Design (Ableton
		Live / FL Studio)

WORK HISTORY

Tesco Colleague (2022 - Present)

Stocking products and customer service.

Honest Burgers (2021 - 2022)

Serving food, drinks, taking payments, and providing customer service.

The Berkeley - Wetherspoons (2018 - 2019) Serving drinks, taking payments, and

customer service.

EDUCATION

Games Technology BSc (Hons) (2019 - 2022)

University of the West of England

Grade: **2:1**

BTEC Extended Diploma in Music Technology

Phone: 07503834590

Level 3 (2015-2017)

Truro College Grade: **DMM**

9 GCSEs (inc. Maths & English) (2012-2015)

Poltair School Grade: **B-C**

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Gaming, Game Design, Programming, Music Production, Building Lego